modders-inc.com 2019-12-14

# Modders-Inc Privacy Page

At Modders-Inc, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Modders-Inc and how it is used.

 **Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**  
Certain visitors to Modders-Inc.com’s website that choose to interact with Modders-Inc.com in ways that require Modders-Inc.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Modders-Inc.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who use our forums to provide a username and email address. In each case, Modders-Inc.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Modders-Inc.com. Modders-Inc.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

 **Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, Modders-Inc makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protcol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Modders-Inc.com uses cookies to help Modders-Inc.com identify and track visitors, their usage of Modders-Inc.com website, and their website access preferences. Modders-Inc.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Modders-Inc.com’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Modders-Inc.com’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

 **Privacy Policy Changes**  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Modders-Inc.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Modders-Inc.com’s sole discretion. Modders-Inc.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

###### Newsletter & emails

If you have subscribed to our newsletter or if you are a member of our website (you can log in) or if you have purchased on our website, there is a good chance you will receive emails from us.

We will only send you emails which you have signed up to receive, or which pertain to the services we provided to you.

To send you emails, we use the name and email address you provide us. Our site also logs the IP address you used when you signed up for the service to prevent abuse of the system.

This website can send emails through the [MailPoet sending service](https://www.mailpoet.com/privacy-notice/). This service allows us to track opens and clicks on our emails. We use this information to improve the content of our newsletters.

No identifiable information is otherwise tracked outside this website except for the email address.

##### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

 ** ** Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

##### Media

If you upload images to the website or into the forums, **_you_** should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

##### Contact forms

By default, WordPress does not include a contact form. If you use a contact form plugin, use this subsection to note what personal data is captured when someone submits a contact form, and how long you keep it. For example, you may note that you keep contact form submissions for a certain period for customer service purposes, but you do not use the information submitted through them for marketing purposes.

##### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

##### Analytics

Google analytics is the method that we use to collect data on visitors to our website. This information is used to see which articles are popular, lest popular, where traffice comes from and what time of the day do we get the most/least amount of traffic.

##### How long we retain your data

We keep contact form entries for six months, analytics records for a year.

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

##### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …. Google Adsense, Google DoubleClick, Amazon,  Vibrant.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Modders-Inc send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Modders-Inc has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Modders-Inc’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
– Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Modders-Inc.  
– Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Modders-Inc and other sites on the internet.  
– Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Google Adsense  
**We are a participant in the Google Adsense Ad Display Program, an advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to third party ads.

 **Amazon  
**We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

Modders-Inc does use code from sources such as facebook, twitter, linkedin, Instagram, Pinterest, AddThis, and others for the sole purpose of allowing visitors and users to share or like content from Modders-Inc. Modders-Inc does not have any control over how this information is collected or used by any of these sites or companies.

Any information collected during any contest or events is solely used by Modders-Inc for the duration of the contest or event and is not sold or used for any marketing purposes by either Modders-Inc or vendors unless it is agreed upon at the time you sign up for a contest or event.

Opt-Out Policy Modders-Inc.com gives users options to opt out wherever practical; such choices include: – Opting not to receive our electronic newsletters when registering for the site – Opting not to receive review site notifications

Unsubscribe Policy Users may unsubscribe from any of our electronic newsletters or site notifications at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of each newsletter or notification.

Use of Collected Information Collecting the information described above enables us to tailor our content to our readers’ needs.

 **Google Privacy Policy** – [Link](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

 **Google Ad Privacy Policy** – [Link](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

 **Facebook Privacy Policy** –[ Link](http://www.facebook.com/help/445588775451827)

 **Twitter Privacy Policy** – [Link](https://twitter.com/privacy)

 **  Amazon Privacy Policy **– [Link](https://services.amazon.com/content/Privacy_Policy.html)

 **AddThis Privacy Policy** – [Link](http://www.addthis.com/privacy#.Twcme9Xp7ao)

 **Patreon Privacy Policy** – [Link](https://www.patreon.com/privacy)

 **Youtube Privacy Policy** – [Link](https://www.youtube.com/static?template=terms)

By default, WordPress does not share any personal data with anyone.

### Third parties

Hummingbird uses the Stackpath Content Delivery Network (CDN). Stackpath may store web log information of site visitors, including IPs, UA, referrer, Location and ISP info of site visitors for 7 days. Files and images served by the CDN may be stored and served from countries other than your own. Stackpath’s privacy policy can be found [here](https://www.stackpath.com/legal/privacy-statement/).

Acceptance of Terms By using the Modders-Inc.com website, you signify your acceptance of this website privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. Your continued use of any Modders-Inc.com site following the posting of changes to these terms will indicate your acceptance of those changes.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at our [contact page](https://www.modders-inc.com/modders-inc-contact-page/)

### Plugin: Smush

Note: Smush does not interact with end users on your website. The only input option Smush has is to a newsletter subscription for site admins only. If you would like to notify your users of this in your privacy policy, you can use the information below.

Smush sends images to the WPMU DEV servers to optimize them for web use. This includes the transfer of EXIF data. The EXIF data will either be stripped or returned as it is. It is not stored on the WPMU DEV servers.

Smush uses the Stackpath Content Delivery Network (CDN). Stackpath may store web log information of site visitors, including IPs, UA, referrer, Location and ISP info of site visitors for 7 days. Files and images served by the CDN may be stored and served from countries other than your own. Stackpath’s privacy policy can be found [here](https://www.stackpath.com/legal/privacy-statement/).

Smush uses a third-party email service (Drip) to send informational emails to the site administrator. The administrator’s email address is sent to Drip and a cookie is set by the service. Only administrator information is collected by Drip.
